sbn.com 2018-12-21

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY
SBN.com Privacy Policy
The Superior Business Network (SBN.com) respects the privacy of our users and
has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting
your privacy. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe for you, as an individual
who is a user of SBN.com or our services, or otherwise provide us with
information through various means such as mail-in entries for sweepstakes or
contests, the information we collect, how that information may be used, with
whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures. We
encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or
services or transacting business with us. SBN.com is part of WOMM, LLC. If you
have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this
Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.
Information we collect about you
We may collect personal information that can identify you such as your name and
email address and other information that does not identify you. When you provide
personal information through our website, the information may be sent to servers
located in the United States and other countries around the world.
       Information you provide - We may collect and store any personal
       information you enter on our website or provide to us in some other
       manner including through surveys conducted on our website. This
       includes identifying information, such as your name, address, e-mail
       address, and telephone number, and, if you transact business with us,
       financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card
       number, type, expiration date or other financial information). We also may
       request information about your interests and activities, your gender and
       age, and other demographic information as well as public information such
       as user ratings and reviews, saved restaurant and event listings, and other
       information you view on the website.
       Information from other sources - We may also periodically obtain both
       personal and non-personal information about you from other businesses,
       business partners, and other third parties and add it to our account
       information or other information we have collected. Examples of
       information that we may receive include: updated delivery and address
       information, purchase history, and additional demographic information.
       Information about others - We may also collect and store personal
       information about other people that you provide to us. If you use our
       website to send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) information that
       may interest them or messages (such as invitations) through our system,

        we may store your personal information, and the personal information of
        each such recipient.
Use of cookies and other technologies to collect information - We use
various technologies to collect information from your computer and about your
activities on our site.
        Information collected automatically - We automatically collect
        information from your browser when you visit our website. This information
        includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times,
        the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously
        accepted from us (see "Cookies" below), and the referring website
        address.
        Cookies - When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one
        or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your
        online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may
        automatically collect information about your online activity on our site,
        such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you
        conduct on our site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you
        can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose
        to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use
        some of the interactive features offered on our website.
        Other Technologies - We may use standard Internet technology, such as
        web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site.
        We also may include web beacons in promotional or other e-mail
        messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been
        opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables
        us to customize the services we offer our website visitors to deliver
        targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our
        online advertising, content, programming or other activities.
        Information collected by third parties - We may allow third parties,
        including our authorized service providers, affiliate companies, advertising
        companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements or provide
        applications and services on our site. These companies may use tracking
        technologies, such as cookies or web beacons, to collect information
        about users who view or interact with their advertisements or use their
        applications and services. Our website does not provide any personal
        information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver
        targeted advertisements and personalize online experiences and gauge
        their effectiveness.

How we use the information we collect
SBN.com may use information that we collect about you to:
        Deliver the products and services that you have requested;
        Manage your account and provide you with customer support;
        Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our
        products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by
        others;
        Communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile
        devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either
        from us, our affiliate companies or other third parties;
        Develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on
        our site and other sites;
        Verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and
        sweepstakes;
        Enforce our terms and conditions;
        Manage our business and
        Perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.
Financial information - We may use financial information or payment method to
process payment for any purchases made on our website, to pre-qualify you for
credit card and other offers that you might find of interest, to protect against or
identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our
business.
Job applicants - If your personal information is submitted through our website
when applying for a position with our company, the information will be used
solely in connection with considering and acting upon your application. We may
retain your personal information for a period of time, but only for the purpose of
considering your application for current or future available positions. This
information may be shared with affiliate companies for the purpose of evaluating
your qualifications for the particular position or other available positions, as well
as with third-party service providers retained by us to collect, maintain and
analyze candidate submissions for job postings.
With whom we share your information
We want you to understand when and with whom we may share personal or
other information we have collected about you or your activities on our web site
or while using our services.
Personal information
We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated below

or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your
personal information shared. We may share personal information with:
      Authorized service providers - We may share your personal information
      with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our
      behalf. These services may include processing credit card payments,
      delivering packages, providing customer service and marketing
      assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our
      website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and
      other features offered through our website. These service providers may
      have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but
      are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.
      Business partners - When you make purchases, reservations or engage
      in promotions offered through our website or our services, we may share
      personal information with the businesses with which we partner to offer
      you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes.
      When you elect to engage in a particular merchant's offer or program, you
      authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that
      merchant.
      Reservation partners - By making reservations on our website for
      services provided by third parties, including government entities, you
      consent to our providing your personal information and reservation
      information to these reservation partners. Sharing this information with our
      reservation partners allows them to contact you using the e-mail address
      or other contact information you provided.
      Direct mail partners - From time to time we may share our postal mailing
      list with selected providers of goods and services that may be of interest to
      you. If you prefer not to receive mailings from these providers, you can
      notify us at any time by sending an email to customerservice@SBN.com
      Our affiliate businesses - We are part of WOMM, LLC. We may share
      information we collect, including personal information, with our affiliate
      companies. Sharing information with our affiliate companies enables us to
      provide you with information about a variety of products and services that
      might interest you. All WOMM, LLC companies comply with this Privacy
      Policy. Our affiliate companies also will comply with applicable privacy and
      security laws and, at a minimum, in any commercial e-mail they send to
      you, will give you the opportunity to choose not to receive such e-mail
      messages in the future.
Other Situations

        We also may disclose your information in response to a subpoena or
        similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation
        from law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or
        exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise
        required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection
        or right available to us.
        When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to
        investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity,
        suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights,
        property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to
        comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to
        enforce our website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.
        In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of
        business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the
        unlikely event of bankruptcy. The personal information that you provide to
        us is an asset of the company and may be included in the assets
        transferred in the event of a substantial corporate transaction.
Any third parties to whom we may disclose personal information may have their
own privacy policies, which describe how they use and disclose personal
information. Those policies will govern use, handling and disclosure of your
personal information once we have shared it with those third parties as described
in this Privacy Policy. If you want to learn more about their privacy practices, we
encourage you to visit the websites of those third parties. These entities or their
servers may be located either inside or outside the United States.
Aggregated and non-personal information - We may share aggregated and
non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We
may also share it with third parties and our affiliate companies to develop and
deliver targeted advertising on our websites and on websites of third parties. We
may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal
information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated
information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for
the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell
our advertisers the number of visitors to our website and the most popular
features or services accessed. This information does not contain any personal
information and may be used to develop website content and services that we
hope you and other users will find of interest and to target content and
advertising. For merchants, we may share your business contact information with
third parties, including but not limited to, business name, address, telephone
number, email address and name of owner or proprietor of the business.

Third-party websites
There are a number of places on our website where you may click on a link to
access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For
example, if you click on an advertisement or a search result on our website, you
may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may
independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from
you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on
those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all
third-party websites you visit by clicking on the "privacy" link typically located at
the bottom of the webpage you are visiting.
How you can access your information
If you have an online account with us, you have the ability to review and update
your personal information online by simply logging into your account. You can
also review and update your personal information by contacting us. More
information about how to contact us is provided below.
Your choices about collection and use of your information
You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in
you being unable to use certain features of our website because such information
may be required in order for you to have personalized recommendations
presented to you; register as a member or user; purchase products or services;
participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or
initiate other transactions on our website. At any time you can choose to no
longer receive commercial or promotional emails or newsletters from us by
logging in with your account information, or by calling SBN.com Customer
Service at 877.4SBNCOM. You also will be given the opportunity, in any
commercial e-mail that we send to you, to opt out of receiving such messages in
the future. It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request. We
may send you other types of transactional and relationship e-mail
communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and
surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. Please
note that changing information in your account, or otherwise opting out of receipt
of promotional email communications will only affect future activities or
communications from us. If we have already provided your information to a third
party (such as an event provider) before you have changed your preferences or
updated your information, you may have to change you preferences directly with
that third party.
How we protect your personal information
We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and

procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from
unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees
are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for
permitted business functions. In addition, we use firewalls to help prevent
unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information.
We want you to feel confident using our website to transact business. However,
no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to
secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your
personal information, searches, or other communications would always remain
secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their
personal information and should avoid sending personal information through
insecure email. Please refer to the Federal Trade Commission's website at
http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm for information about how to
protect yourself against identity theft.
Blogs, bulletin boards, reviews and chat rooms
We may provide areas on our websites where you can post information about
yourself and others and communicate with others, as well as post reviews of
businesses, products, establishments, contractors, and the like, or upload
content (e.g. pictures, videos, audio files, etc.). Such postings are governed by
our Terms of Use. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or
when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you
voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly viewable web pages, that
information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others.
For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited
messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may
do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise
discretion and caution with respect to your personal information.
Children's privacy
Our website is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect personal
information from children under the age of 13.
Visiting our websites from outside the United States
This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our website
from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our website from outside
the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to,
stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and
our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the
United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in
your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure
that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your

information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom
we share it as described in this privacy policy.
No Rights of Third Parties
This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require
disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices
and services. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or
share your personal information, we will notify you by sending an email to the
email address you most recently provided us in your account, profile or
registration (unless we do not have such an address), and/or by prominently
posting notice of the changes on our website. We recommend that you check our
website from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy
or any of our other policies.
How to contact us
SBN.COM
440 Fair Drive, Suite 200
Costa Mesa, CA 92626
949.873.1001
www.SBN.com
Cookies:
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record keeping
purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A
session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it
easier for you to navigate our website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard
drive for an extended period of time.
You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings.(Click
"Help" in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, some of the
features and services of our website may not function properly.
Web Beacons:
Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics
with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the
online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies that are
stored on the user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly
on the web pages (or in email) and are about the size of the period at the end of

this sentence.
Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count
users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also
may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an
online advertisement displayed on a third-party website.
